[
    {
    "question":"Who is Gurpreet chawla ?",
    "optionA" :"Web developer",
    "optionB" :"Photographer",
    "optionC" :"Content writer",
    "optionD" :"Data scientist",
    "answer":"Web developer"
},

{
    "question":"What is Gurpreet chawla's age ? ",
    "optionA" :"20yr",
    "optionB" :"21yr",
    "optionC" :"22yr",
    "optionD" :"23yr",
    "answer":"23yr"
},

{
    "question":"What is Gurpreet chawla's religion ?",
    "optionA" :"Hindu",
    "optionB" :"Muslim",
    "optionC" :"Sikh",
    "optionD" :"Christian",
    "answer":"Sikh"
},

{
    "question":"Who is Gurpreet's mother ?",
    "optionA" :"Mrs.Inderjeet chawla",
    "optionB" :"Mrs.Rajinder chawla",
    "optionC" :"Mrs.Manmeet chawla",
    "optionD" :"Mrs.Juhi chawla",
    "answer":"Mrs.Inderjeet chawla"
},

{
    "question":"Height of Gurpreet chawla?",
    "optionA" :"5.4ft",
    "optionB" :"5.6ft",
    "optionC" :"5.7ft",
    "optionD" :"5.5ft",
    "answer":"5.6ft"
},

{
    "question":"Weight of Gurpreet chawla?",
    "optionA" :"55kg",
    "optionB" :"56kg",
    "optionC" :"57kg",
    "optionD" :"58kg",
    "answer":"57kg"
},

{
    "question":"Gurpreet chawla's colleges?",
    "optionA" :"G.L Bajaj",
    "optionB" :"Galgotias university",
    "optionC" :"Amity university",
    "optionD" :"Lovely Profesional University",
    "answer":"Galgotias university"
},

{
    "question":"When is Gurpreet Chawla's birthday?",
    "optionA" :"23rd may 1997",
    "optionB" :"25th may 1997",
    "optionC" :"30th may 1997",
    "optionD" :"27th may 1997",
    "answer":"30th may 1997"
},

{
    "question":"Where is Gurpreet Chawla from?",
    "optionA" :"Rudrapur",
    "optionB" :"Greater Noida",
    "optionC" :"Bareilly",
    "optionD" :"Delhi",
    "answer":"Rudrapur"
},

{
    "question":"Who is Gurpreet Chawlaâ€™s father?",
    "optionA" :"Mr Harpreet Chawla",
    "optionB" :"Mr. Kulvir Chawla",
    "optionC" :"Mr.Jagjeet Chawla",
    "optionD" :"Mr.Gurpreet Chawla",
    "answer":"Mr. Kulvir Chawla"
}
]